Wynonah Rebutar

+63 929-311-8425 ∣ wynonahrebutar@gmail.com ∣ Taguig City, 1633 LinkedIn 🗹

A mastery-oriented and resourceful astronomy graduate, experienced in collaborative data analysis within the scientific field. Enthusiastic about utilizing skills and acquiring new knowledge to deliver impactful contributions to the business sector.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Magic, Inc. Apr 2021 - Feb 2024

Creative Solutions Specialist | Freelancer

- Assisted managers in leading a fast-paced operations team, ensuring efficient decision-making and delivery of high-quality output within established timelines for clients.
- Handled diverse tasks such as executive calendar management and lead generation, using Microsoft Office and Google Workspace tools.

National Astronomical Research Institute of Thailand (NARIT)

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

Stellar Studies/Open Clusters Group | Intern

• Utilized Python to replicate research findings from "A Wise Census of Young Stellar Objects in Canis Major" (Fischer et al., 2016), using large datasets from NASA's AllWISE Catalog, and created visual representations of the analyzed data.

EDUCATION

Rizal Technological University BS Astronomy major in Astrophysics

Stellar Student (1.49 GWA) Aug 2019 - June 2023

Taguig Science High School STEM

with Honors June 2013 - Apr 2019

SKILLS

Analytics: Exploratory Data Analysis, Data Mining

Spreadsheets: Excel, Google Sheets, Pivot Tables, VLOOKUP, INDEX/MATCH

Programming: Python, SQL

Visualization: Matplotlib, Tableau, Excel Charts

Soft Skills: Proactivity, Critical Thinking, Team Collaboration, Organizational Proficiency

CERTIFICATIONS

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate ☑

Statistics for Data Science and Business Analysis by 365 Careers 🖸 Data Analytics Bootcamp by DataSense Analytics and Future Skills Now

PROJECTS

Exploratory Data Analysis on the Hipparcos Catalog 2

Co-author

Replicated the Hertzsprung-Russell Diagram using Python to show the relationship between temperature and luminosity or the absolute magnitude and color index of stars from the catalog.

Cyclistic Data Analysis 🖸

Used Python and Tableau to prepare Cyclistic's 2022 dataset and analyze its usage patterns to help develop a business strategy that encourages and sustains membership.